thenextdigit.com 2019-01-25

# Privacy Policy | TND

The Next Digit news group refers to the current Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) to handle the personal data that is gathered either intentionally or unintentionally, either directly or indirectly from returning visitors upon their visit on the website. The Next Digit (“we”, or “us”) uses various techniques to collect personal information through personal computers, mobile devices and interactive services.

We pay much attention to our privacy policy because we understand how relevant this data is to you. The current Privacy Policy is our commitment to ensure the security of our readers’ personal information. By means of the present Privacy Policy, we intend to explain our readers what ‘personal information’ signifies to us and the methods we will use to collect such data from our website. The following lines will, introduce you, therefore, to the purpose of our data collection and will reveal the cases when the information will be disclosed to third parties.

Before you continue reading our general terms and regulations, we would like to stop and ask you to carefully read the present Privacy Policy if you are accessing our news platform for the first time. There could be changes in our Privacy Policy from time to time. Readers are advised, for this reason, to revise these post every once in a while and take notice of all possible changes. READERS ACCESSING OUT WEBSITE ARE AUTOMATICALLY AGREEING TO THE TERMS AND REGULATIONS OF OUR PRIVACY POLICY. VISITORS, WHO DO NOT AGREE WITH OUR PRIVACY POLICY RULES SHOULD IMMEDIATELY TERMINATE THEIR VISIT AND LEAVE OUR NEWS WEBSITE.

## **Personal and Connected Information**

In accordance with the current Privacy Policy, our website distinguishes between two types of personal information and these are: information that is personally provided by our readers and information that is automatically collected upon readers’ visit on our website. By personal information, we refer to personal details related to names, addresses, emails, telephone numbers and similar data, which is provided by readers while subscribing to one of our services or creating their own account. The non-personal information, that is, the information that is automatically collected when users enter our website, comprises data that is connected to a reader’s online person, but not exclusively related. IP addresses, domain names of Internet providers, web browsing preferences and other similar details are usually labeled as non-personal information. Our website uses special algorithms to collect information about our readers’ favorite search terms, websites, as well as the time they usually spend on our pages.

We attribute great important to our readers’ privacy; therefore, we will take care not to disclose any of their personal information without their prior consent. We will only use this data to help our website administrators stay in contact with our readers, contact them and improve our online services for our customers. We put our readers’ preferences first; therefore, we may sometimes ask our readers to take part in online survey so we can better understand them. Occasionally, we may share your data with third parties that are in charge of our customer support and promotional services. Readers, who do not want to share their contact details with our third party operators can de-register from our services and/or specify their wish for their personal data not to be shared with affiliated companies. We may also use your personal details for our vendors, particularly when hired to carry out services on our behalf. Vendors carry out marketing promotions, data analysis, customer services, etc.

Our readers need to understand that it is very important for us to gather their personal and connected information because we can thus better understand their online behavior and their preferences. Our company and our affiliated companies have the liberty to freely use this data to analyze website traffic, online trends and to create promotional campaigns for our online services. Our website uses cookies, email addresses and/or IP addresses to collect non-personal information from our readers, but there could be other methods we could use in the future, as well.

### **Revisiting Your Personal Data**

Readers have the opportunity to access their personal accounts and revisit their personal information at any time. If the service is unavailable for reasons that do not relate to us, readers can contact us by filling the Contact Us forms and inform us about their problems and complaints.

### **Personal Data Protection**

Since we care so much about our readers’ privacy, we have used the most advanced security tools and software to protect our visitors as they enter our pages. We guarantee, you, the reader that your account information is always safe with us and that nobody will access, alter or destroy your personal information. Nevertheless, we need our readers’ collaboration because no security measure is completely flawless and we could confront ourselves with unwanted situations. We advise subscribers to protect their bank account details and to avoid sharing such information on unprotected pages.

### **Advertising Content**

While visiting our website pages, readers may stumble across advertising content delivered by third party companies. Links to third-party providers could also be displayed on our pages, depending on the business relationships we have established with them. The Next Digit is not to be held responsible for the advertising content displayed by third-party companies or the services and the companies they promote.

Readers should be informed that third parties may use their own systems of data collection from our readers. The Next Digit is not to be held responsible for their mistakes as the provisions of our Privacy Policy are replaced in this case with the terms and regulations of the third-party providers. Readers have to consult the Privacy Policies of the third-party companies and contact them if they have any questions about them.

### **Non-U.S. Readers and Visitors**

The Internet is an infinite space, without geographical boundaries or confinements of any kind. Yet, the borders in our real life are many times continued on the Internet to prevent problems and complications. Consequently, we expect our website, which has been designed in keeping with local laws, to be primarily visited by U.S. residents. Should there be non-U.S. readers, they must know that they are wholeheartedly welcome as long as they consent to our Terms of Service and our Privacy Policy pages. We are using U.S. laws and regulations to ensure the protection of personal information on our website, but readers should double check as there may be differences between the U.S. and the non-U.S. legal frameworks.

### **Children**

Our website has been designed for grownups, who have already accomplished 13 years old. Readers, who are not 13 are prohibited to use our website and our website pages. Nevertheless, there is not age-gradation on the content of our website as is the case with many other online platforms.

We do not collect personal information from underage readers, who are also younger than 13 years old. Tutors, parents, guardians, who have found out that an underage user has provided personal information on our website are asked to immediately contact us to remove the said data. Our website administrators, in their turn, will contact us as soon as they receive information that a child has provided personal information on our website. The Next Digit takes full responsibility to remove such information should there be any notifications in this sense.

### **Contact Us**

Readers, visitors and returning visitors can address us questions, can make suggestions and file complaints in relation to our Privacy Policy by accessing our Contact Us page. We will read all their emails and respond to them in the shortest time possible. The Next Digit takes its liberty to ignore those messages that do not comply with the general rules of netiquette and/or are not grounded on solid arguments.

### **Sole Statement**

The terms of our Privacy Policy as presented on our website, is our sole statement of privacy policy. For that matter, we will not consider other versions, except for the revisited Privacy Policies that we post on our website. Members are not allowed to make changes in our Privacy Policy without having the prior consent of our editorial group.
